const level2Questions = [
  
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 17?",
        options: ["20", "19", "18", "21"],
        answer: "19"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 93?",
        options: ["96", "97", "94", "95"],
        answer: "95"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 41?",
        options: ["44", "43", "42", "45"],
        answer: "43"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 72?",
        options: ["70", "73", "71", "74"],
        answer: "74"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 3?",
        options: ["4", "6", "5", "2"],
        answer: "5"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 56?",
        options: ["57", "55", "54", "58"],
        answer: "58"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 28?",
        options: ["29", "31", "27", "30"],
        answer: "30"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 85?",
        options: ["86", "88", "84", "87"],
        answer: "87"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 10?",
        options: ["8", "9", "12", "11"],
        answer: "12"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 49?",
        options: ["50", "48", "47", "51"],
        answer: "51"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 64?",
        options: ["63", "65", "62", "66"],
        answer: "66"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 2?",
        options: ["1", "4", "0", "3"],
        answer: "4"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 98?",
        options: ["96", "97", "100", "99"],
        answer: "100"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 37?",
        options: ["38", "36", "39", "35"],
        answer: "39"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 7?",
        options: ["8", "5", "6", "9"],
        answer: "9"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 20?",
        options: ["21", "22", "18", "19"],
        answer: "22"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 79?",
        options: ["78", "80", "77", "81"],
        answer: "81"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 61?",
        options: ["60", "63", "59", "62"],
        answer: "63"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 16?",
        options: ["14", "18", "15", "17"],
        answer: "18"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 95?",
        options: ["96", "93", "97", "94"],
        answer: "97"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 87?",
        options: ["86", "89", "85", "88"],
        answer: "89"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 1?",
        options: ["3", "0", "2", "-1"],
        answer: "3"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 68?",
        options: ["69", "70", "67", "66"],
        answer: "70"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 32?",
        options: ["33", "31", "30", "34"],
        answer: "34"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 52?",
        options: ["51", "54", "50", "53"],
        answer: "54"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 96?",
        options: ["97", "98", "94", "95"],
        answer: "98"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 9?",
        options: ["10", "8", "11", "7"],
        answer: "11"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 44?",
        options: ["43", "46", "42", "45"],
        answer: "46"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 71?",
        options: ["70", "72", "69", "73"],
        answer: "73"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 53?",
        options: ["55", "51", "52", "54"],
        answer: "55"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 39?",
        options: ["41", "37", "38", "40"],
        answer: "41"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 23?",
        options: ["24", "22", "25", "21"],
        answer: "25"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 5?",
        options: ["6", "3", "4", "7"],
        answer: "7"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 83?",
        options: ["82", "85", "84", "81"],
        answer: "85"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 65?",
        options: ["66", "64", "67", "63"],
        answer: "67"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 76?",
        options: ["74", "77", "75", "78"],
        answer: "78"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 35?",
        options: ["34", "37", "36", "33"],
        answer: "37"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 14?",
        options: ["15", "13", "16", "12"],
        answer: "16"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 25?",
        options: ["24", "27", "26", "23"],
        answer: "27"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 70?",
        options: ["69", "72", "71", "68"],
        answer: "72"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 31?",
        options: ["32", "30", "33", "29"],
        answer: "33"


    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 86?",
        options: ["85", "87", "88", "84"],
        answer: "88"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 60?",
        options: ["61", "59", "62", "58"],
        answer: "62"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 78?",
        options: ["77", "80", "76", "79"],
        answer: "80"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 13?",
        options: ["12", "15", "14", "11"],
        answer: "15"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 58?",
        options: ["59", "57", "60", "56"],
        answer: "60"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 21?",
        options: ["22", "23", "20", "19"],
        answer: "23"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 81?",
        options: ["82", "80", "83", "79"],
        answer: "83"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 45?",
        options: ["46", "47", "44", "43"],
        answer: "47"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 6?",
        options: ["8", "7", "5", "4"],
        answer: "8"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 11?",
        options: ["12", "9", "13", "10"],
        answer: "13"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 48?",
        options: ["47", "50", "49", "46"],
        answer: "50"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 80?",
        options: ["82", "79", "81", "78"],
        answer: "82"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 19?",
        options: ["18", "21", "20", "17"],
        answer: "21"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 97?",
        options: ["99", "96", "98", "95"],
        answer: "99"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 69?",
        options: ["71", "68", "70", "67"],
        answer: "71"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 24?",
        options: ["26", "25", "27", "23"],
        answer: "26"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 74?",
        options: ["76", "73", "72", "75"],
        answer: "76"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 54?",
        options: ["55", "53", "56", "52"],
        answer: "56"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 67?",
        options: ["69", "68", "66", "65"],
        answer: "69"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 38?",
        options: ["40", "37", "39", "36"],
        answer: "40"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 18?",
        options: ["20", "17", "19", "16"],
        answer: "20"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 8?",
        options: ["10", "7", "9", "6"],
        answer: "10"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 62?",
        options: ["64", "61", "63", "60"],
        answer: "64"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 29?",
        options: ["31", "28", "30", "27"],
        answer: "31"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 50?",
        options: ["52", "49", "51", "48"],
        answer: "52"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 12?",
        options: ["14", "11", "13", "10"],
        answer: "14"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 59?",
        options: ["61", "58", "60", "57"],
        answer: "61"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 89?",
        options: ["91", "88", "90", "87"],
        answer: "91"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 27?",
        options: ["29", "26", "28", "25"],
        answer: "29"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 36?",
        options: ["38", "35", "37", "34"],
        answer: "38"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 84?",
        options: ["86", "83", "85", "82"],
        answer: "86"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 75?",
        options: ["77", "74", "76", "73"],
        answer: "77"
    },
    {


        question: "Add +2 to: 55?",
        options: ["57", "54", "56", "53"],
        answer: "57"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 0?",
        options: ["2", "-1", "1", "-2"],
        answer: "2"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 63?",
        options: ["65", "62", "64", "61"],
        answer: "65"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 47?",
        options: ["49", "46", "48", "45"],
        answer: "49"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 99?",
        options: ["101", "98", "100", "97"],
        answer: "101"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 73?",
        options: ["75", "72", "74", "71"],
        answer: "75"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 91?",
        options: ["93", "90", "92", "89"],
        answer: "93"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 43?",
        options: ["45", "42", "44", "41"],
        answer: "45"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 30?",
        options: ["32", "29", "31", "28"],
        answer: "32"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 15?",
        options: ["17", "14", "16", "13"],
        answer: "17"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 51?",
        options: ["53", "50", "52", "49"],
        answer: "53"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 94?",
        options: ["96", "93", "95", "92"],
        answer: "96"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 22?",
        options: ["24", "21", "23", "20"],
        answer: "24"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 57?",
        options: ["59", "56", "58", "55"],
        answer: "59"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 46?",
        options: ["48", "45", "47", "44"],
        answer: "48"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 90?",
        options: ["92", "89", "91", "88"],
        answer: "92"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 26?",
        options: ["28", "25", "27", "24"],
        answer: "28"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 82?",
        options: ["84", "81", "83", "80"],
        answer: "84"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 4?",
        options: ["6", "3", "5", "2"],
        answer: "6"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 40?",
        options: ["42", "39", "41", "38"],
        answer: "42"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 88?",
        options: ["90", "87", "89", "86"],
        answer: "90"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 66?",
        options: ["68", "65", "67", "64"],
        answer: "68"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 42?",
        options: ["44", "41", "43", "40"],
        answer: "44"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 77?",
        options: ["79", "76", "78", "75"],
        answer: "79"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 92?",
        options: ["94", "91", "93", "90"],
        answer: "94"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 34?",
        options: ["36", "33", "35", "32"],
        answer: "36"
    },
    {
        question: "Add +2 to: 33?",
        options: ["35", "34", "36", "32"],
        answer: "35"
    }
 
  ];
  
  export default level2Questions